<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root>
    <section topic="intro">
        <title>Belgian Waffles</title>
        <para>Chef Ludo Lefebvre’s Belgian Waffles are light and crispy, with plenty of deep, large
            squares for butter, syrup, whipped cream, and fresh berries. Be careful not to overmix
            the egg whites which can cause the batter to clump. To prepare the batter ahead of time,
            simply omit the egg whites until ready to make waffles. Then let the batter come to room
            temperature, and gently fold in eggs.</para>

        <author>By Ludo Lefebvre</author>
        <pubDate>Published on November 1, 2018</pubDate>
        <source>Source: Food&amp;Wine. <url
                ref="https://www.foodandwine.com/recipes/belgian-waffles">URL:
                https://www.foodandwine.com/recipes/belgian-waffles</url>
        </source>
        <time type="active" quant="20" unit="min">Active Time: 20 mins</time>
        <time type="complete" quant="50" unit="min">Total Time: 50 mins</time>
        <yield>Yield: 5 waffles</yield>
    </section>
    <teachableMoment><!-- 2023-01-26 ebb: This is an XML comment, and we use it to chat about the code with others who are reading it.
    Technically what's here is separate from the document, but commenting on it in some way.
    The tagging for this element is illustrating camelCase in markup.--> In mathematics, 4 &lt;
        6 .</teachableMoment>

    <section topic="ingredients">Ingredients 1 3/4 cups all-purpose flour 2 teaspoons granulated
        sugar 2 teaspoons kosher salt 3 large eggs, separated 1 1/4 cups water 1 teaspoon pure
        vanilla extract 8 ounces unsalted butter, melted, plus more for greasing Quartered
        strawberries and unsweetened whipped cream, for serving Confectioners’ sugar, for
        dusting</section>

    <section topic="directions">
        <heading>Directions</heading>
        <step n="1">In a large bowl, whisk the flour with the sugar and salt. In a medium bowl, beat
            the egg yolks with the water and vanilla. Stir the wet ingredients into the dry
            ingredients, then stir in the butter until incorporated.</step>

        <step n="2">In a medium bowl, using a handheld electric mixer, beat the egg whites at
            medium-high speed until soft peaks form, about 2 minutes. Fold them into the
            batter.</step>

        <step n="3">Preheat the oven to <temp quant="200" unit="degrees-F">200°</temp>. Heat a
            Belgian waffle iron, then grease it with melted butter. Spoon <meas>1 cup of the
                batter</meas> into the iron, close the top and cook until the waffle is golden, 6
            minutes. Transfer the waffle the prepared baking sheet and keep warm in the oven. Repeat
            with the remaining batter. Top the waffles with quartered strawberries and unsweetened
            whipped cream. Dust with confectioners' sugar and serve.</step>
    </section>

    <section>ADVERTISEMENT Local Offers Erie, PA 16509 Target Logo Featured Products Offer for
        Unbleached All Purpose Flour - 5lbs - Good &amp; Gather™ Unbleached All Purpose Flour - 5lbs
        - Good &amp; Gather™ All-purpose flour is great for all baking needs Offer for Granulated
        Sugar - 4lbs - Good &amp; Gather™ Granulated Sugar - 4lbs - Good &amp; Gather™ Perfect for
        baking or as a sweetener for beverages Offer for Grade A Large Eggs - 12ct - Good &amp;
        Gather™ Grade A Large Eggs - 12ct - Good &amp; Gather™ Grade A Large Eggs make an excellent
        staple in your kitchen Offer for Unsalted Butter - 1lb - Good &amp; Gather™ Unsalted Butter
        - 1lb - Good &amp; Gather™ Ideal for cooking, baking or using as a spread</section>
</root>
